export const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      'What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?',
    answer: '90°',
    options: ['45°', '90°', '60°'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?',
    answer: 'right angled',
    options: ['obtuse', 'acute', 'right angled'],
  },
  {
    question: 'A triangle can have',
    answer: 'one right angle',
    options: ['one right angle', 'two right angles'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following can form a right angled triangle?',
    answer: '12, 16, 20',
    options: ['14, 15, 26', '12, 16, 20'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following triangles are always similar?',
    answer: 'Equilateral triangle',
    options: ['Equilateral triangle', 'Isosceles triangle'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'If one angle of a triangle is obtuse, then which one of the following is the possible measure of remaining angles?',
    answer: '100°',
    options: ['100°', '85°'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'If the largest angle in a triangle is 70°, what is the least possible value of the smallest angle of the triangle?',
    answer: '30°',
    options: ['30°', '10°'],
  },
  {
    question: 'The perimeter of scalene triangle with sides a, b, c is',
    answer: 'a + b + c',
    options: ['a + b + c', '2a', 'None of these'],
  },
  {
    question: 'A scalene triangle has ___ lines of symmetry',
    answer: 'no',
    options: ['two', 'no', '15'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'There is a right triangle PQR where: angle Q = 90°; angle P = angle R. What is the measure of angles P and R?',
    answer: '45°',
    options: ['85°', '65°', '45°'],
  },
]
